<localizationDictionary culture="en">
  <texts>
    <text value="Shanghai Bizhi Technology Co., Ltd. will give special protection to the privacy and security of your personal information. We will make you feel happy and value for money when using Bizhi's high-quality services, and feel safe because your privacy interests are respected. In this clause, we will inform you what information we collect and how to deal with it\ N \ nwe have updated the privacy policy according to the regulatory requirements, and hereby explain to you as follows: \ n \ N1. Enable the SD card read-write function to upload documents\ N2. Allow photographing function, which is used to update personal avatar\ N3. Positioning function is allowed, which is used to punch in the attendance system\ N4. Allow access to the calendar, which is used to synchronize the schedule of lvzhihui with the system calendar\ N5. Allow SMS short message sending function (send_sms sensitive information behavior). This permission is used to send short messages to lawyers of case customers\ N6. Integrate Baidu positioning SDK to punch in and locate attendance\ N7. Integrated Alibaba cloud push (Android SDK v3.7.1): get device identification information (MAC address, IMEI / IMSI), device model information, \ n [com. Huawei. HMS] [com. Aliyun] [com. Alipay] [com. Heytap. MSP] [com. Xiaomi. Push] to push user messages\ N8. If you plan to stop using the client system and want to cancel the relevant account opened in our company, you can contact our customer service personnel or the management personnel of your company to provide account cancellation service for you (customer service hotline: + 86 – 400 – 821 – 3228)\ N \ nthe above permissions are system public permissions. If you want to turn on or off permissions, you can change the status in settings - Application Management - Legal intelligence - permission management (the setting paths of each manufacturer may be inconsistent, you can refer to the manufacturer's setting instructions)" name="ContentPrivacyPolicy" />

    </texts>
</localizationDictionary>
